Tufts Criterion UP053
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Criterion, 1968 -- 1993; UP053.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 8 Volumes
  - Criterion, Winter, 1987; UP053.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Juan Alvarez] Recipient of fellowship from the Consortium for graduate study in Management; [Alumni council] List of candidates; [Adler, Andrew] President of newly-formed local prtnership called Webb-Adler, Inc. in Dallas. p. 27; Aeppel, Timothy (F'85)-Staff writer for the Christian Science Monitor in Washington, DC; married Glyn Ferguson 9/7/ 86, p. 30.; Susan (Whilton) Agusti [F 77]. Announces birth of daughter, Jordan Elizabeth. Mark Ainsberg (1982). Product manager with Data General in Westboro, Ma. Married Ellen Rosenberg 7/6/86 in Huntington, NY. Mark H. Allison (49) Licensed sales associate for Murphy Realty-Better Homes and Gardens. [Alumni 1987] Ballot lists trustee council candidates, p. 20. [Alumni 1987] Alumni adventures: May Wonderland, p. 21. [Alumni 1987] Building alumni-student career bridge, p. 21. [Alumni 1987] Travel-athon set for June, p. 22. [Alumni 1987] Tuftonia's Week, p. 22.
  - Criterion, Spring, 1987; UP053.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
    Alumni association salutes 11 outstanding seniors with senior awards; Loius D. Abbey III (D '67). Vice chairman of the Department of Oral Pathology at the Medical College of Virginia in Richmond, pioneering use of computers in dentistry and medicine. (page 25). Lucien P. Adams (E'30). Death of, June 27, 1986. Walter Adamson (F 48). Named professor emeritus at Bridgewater State College, Bridgewater, MA; [Agam, Hasmy Bin-F'81] Malaysian ambassador to Libya, p. 30. Ellen Albanese (1971) Editor of the "Country Gazette" has been recognized for excellence in writing. [Ramon E. Alonso F68] President of Del E. Webb Commercial Properties in Phoenix, AZ, pg. 25. [Alumni 1987] Civil engineering grads hold dinner, p. 20. [Alumni 1987] Eliot-Pearson alums: "close knit," p. 21.
  - Criterion, Summer, 1987; UP053.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni weekend] Photoessay; Letter to the editor clarifying origin of senior awards from Leon Lieber [D1929] former president of Alumni association; Alumni association honors nine: Rocco J. Carzo (athletics director), Allan H. Clemow [E1965], Grant E. Curtis [A1942], Harriet Gaffny Palmieri [J1945], C. June Tow [J1962], Theresa Pease, Michelle B. Tougas, Elisa J. Vega [J1987], Lon Curtis (faculty); Normal Alpert [M1957] Appointed Medical director of the NORCAP Center in Norfolk, MA. Paula (Degruttola) Aaronson '1970, program director for the French Library in Boston, announces the birth of her daughter, Alexandra Leigh, March 3. p. 23; [Admissions][Alumni 1987] Alumni one-on-one with prospective students. p. 13.; Matthew J. Ahern [1986]. Commisioned second lieutenant in the United States Air Force. Henry Akina ('77) Prominent director in Berlin also acts in german film. Seth J. Allen ('81) National import director of Consolidated Distilled Products. [Alumni 1987] Medical/Dental alumni have spring reunions, p. 14.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1987; UP053.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    Veterinarian on staff of Washington County Veterinary hospital in Wakefield, RI; [Deborah B. Alport, G1975] Teaches English at Brookline High School, married Dr. David J. Wyler 5/17/1987 in Newton, MA; Richard L. Abbott (1967). Lectured in opthamology at hospitals in Singapore and Bangkok. Todd Abedon (1987). General manager of the Rhode Island Gulls Basketball Team; [Adkins, Alison (Corner)] Retired from teaching to be at home w/children, participates in various sports with them. pp. 27-28. Adelphi University 1987-88. Dental School seals agreement with Adelphi.; Rev. Ralph Ahlberg [1956]. New minister of the Round Hill Community Church in Round Hill, Ct. Susan L. Allen ('65) Named Secondary Physical Education Teacher of the the Year. [Alumni 1987-88] Alumni organizations news, p. 18.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1988; UP053.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni weekend] Festivities planned; [Alumni council] Ballots list trustee, council candidates; [Alumni association] Distinguished service award presented to six: Maxwell Burstein [E1945], Jefferson G. Cicia [A1958], Leslie H. Gelb [A1959], Brian O'Connell [A1953], Inez Smith Reid [J1959], William B. Richardson [A1970][G1971]; David Albert (1976) Promoted executive director. Catherine Alexander ('63) Executive director of Winchester Chamber of Commerce is also founder/director of Co-operative Theater for Children. Death of (6/11/87) Norman L. Alhadeff (M 79). Bruce Allen (faculty) Co-recipient, with Lawrence H. Ford, of $46,000 grant from the National Science Foundation. Robin Allinson (77) Producer/director, currently producing special called "Backstage," married Jeffery Smalley 4/26/87.
  - Criterion, Spring/Summer, 1987; UP053.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
    [Alumni weekend] Alumni make a comeback; Tufts service citations presented: Joseph J. Byrne [administrative health science], Carla W. Ricci[associate prov. research], Robert Evans [LA1988], Heather Barry [LA1988]; [Alumni association] Outstanding seniors to be recognized with seniors awards; [Alumni association] Distinguished service award presented to six: Maxwell Burstein [E1945], Jefferson G. Cicia [A1958], Leslie H. Gelb [A1959], Brian O'Connell [A1953], Inez Smith Reid [J1959], William B. Richardson [A1970][G1971]; Lawrence K. Altman [M1962] medical correspondant for The New York Times; Recipient of Seniors Award, 1988, [David E. Able] p. 20; [Alfred Aborjaily (M53)] died Nov. 20, 1987. p.34. Erica Adams (Museum 1987). Photographer. Randolph K. Adams. Reassigned to pentagon in August 1987. Beth Adelson (faculty). Awarded $30,000 from National Science Foundation; [ Adler, Alan G.] Assoc. prof. & director of internal medicine at Hahnemann University Hospital. P. 31. Leonard I. Albert (E 42) Died 10/14/87. Spring/Summer 1987
  - Criterion, Fall, 1988; UP053.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alfred A. Amendola [1969][G1979] A deputy director in National Institute for Occupational safety and health, Promoted within company; [Alumni/ae]Upholding tradition, Dental alums, Medical reunion, Class of 1963 reunion, "Tufts at Home" video, Class of 1938 reunion, In the field; Bank of Boston offers Tufts Mastercard or Tufts Gold Master Card to Tufts graduates; [Alumni relations] Seeking amateur photographers for contest for homecoming, Robert Azzi to create pictorial book; [Alumni directory] Alumni survey sent for updated directory; [Alumni association] Pictorial book Tufts University, A Photographic Portrait by Robert Azzi available; [Micheal R. Malkin A1965, G1970] Award winning playwright, director, writer and puppeteer; [Charles Altekruse, F1985] Member of U.S. Olympic rowing team in Seoul, Korea, summer 1988; [Phillip Alston] Re-elected rapporteur of U.N. committee; [Maureen Alophonse LA1987] Newlywed expects to be assigned to Swiss bank in NY; Mohammed Abdel-Wahab (F 63). Returned to Cairo.; [Advocate, Karen '78] Financial manager married 12/20/86. p. 38. [AIDS] Nancy Katz, production coordinator for The Names Project, AIDS quilt. p. 28. [Albertini, David] Vet. School biologists break genetic code. Death of (6/9/88) Sandra (Cochrane) Alexanian. Death of (5/9/88) Frank H. Allen III (F85). Melissa (Mueller) Allen ( F'82) Birth of daughter. [Alumni and Faculty, Famous] Bry, Ellen 1973, Actress ("Shirley Daniels") on "St. Elsewhere" t.v. program from three and a half seasons, p. 36-37.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1989; UP053.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] China travel/study trip; [Alumni weekend] Cavalcade of classes, Medical school date set; Alumni Trustees election, James H. Farrell [E1959], Brian O'Connell [A1953], JoAnn Sher [J1963], Gordon Wood [A1955]; [Alumni relations] Internship program, Travel opportunities; [Alumni council] Dental school election: Robert Chapman [A1963][D1967], John Guinta [A1958][D1966], Steven Chandler [E1962], Nancy Jones Cicia [J1959], Samuel Duboc [E1984], Elaine Kasparian [J1958], Robert H. Lane [E1965], Richard A. Meserve [A1966], Donald Northrup [A1963], Nicholas Paleologos [A1975], Anna Phillips [J1982], David VanCleve, Joseph Zona; [Alumni council] Continuing education committee sponsors "A view from the bridge"; [Alumni association] Tufts travel/study program; [Alumni association] Election; [Alumni association] Interimship program; Tuftonians in power in Washington D.C.[Dante Caputo; Lauro F. Cavazos; Charles H. Dallara; Thomas R. Pickering]; [Denise (Liling) Abadi] Eliot Pearson 78 relocated to Florida.; Elsie Acerra (Friend) 1930 married 50 years. p. 38. Marino Acera (E'37). Married 50 years. Retired; [Administration] Boards of Overseers: feature. pp. 26-27.; [AIDS] Dewolfe, Mark Mosher (A76, G76) (photo) Died, 7/16/88, feature article. p. 45. [AIDS] Louis Lasagna named to panel at Sackler, p. 37. [Al-Attas, Agil Salem] (F 84) Promoted. Death of (8/15/88) David H. Allard (A73). Woody Allen (1989) Exhibition, Wessell. Marsha [Cowan] Alperin Client Services Officer, pg. 41. Thomas Alperin [A81] Real estate, pg. 41. [Alumni 1988-89] Beelzebubs, p. 30.
  - Criterion, Spring/Summer, 1989; UP053.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Amalgamates]Entertain trolley riders at commencement, First foreign appearance in Quebec; [Alumni/ae]Veterinary school 4th reunion, Sports facillities available, Gathered in Quebec for Amalgamates, Cape cod Tufts club and Susan Nickerson [J1979], [G1981] trying to save the cape; [Alumni/ae]List of Alumni alliance leaders; [Alumni weekend] Photoessay; [Alumni trustees] Elections: Alumni council, Brian O'Connell [A1953], JoAnn Sher [J1963]; [Alumni relations] Tufts University wall clock, Co-creator of special Mastercard for Tuftonians, Co-sponsors Tufts Interimship program; [Alumni relations] Alumni directory due fall 1989; Alumni council elections; [Alumni council] Homecoming committee; [Alumni council] Liberal arts elections: Nancy Jones Cicia [J1959], Steven W. Chandler [E1963], Elaine G. Kasparian [J1958], Elena Massarotti [J1980][M1984] Richard Meserve [A1966], Donald Northrup [A1963], Anna Phillips [J1982], Joseph Zona [E1974]; [Alumni council] Continuing education committee plans Enlightenment series; [alumni center] Homecoming and class reunions; [Alumni association] Veterinary school; [Alumni association] Tufts University wall clock; [Alumni association] Senior awards recipients: Jennifer Abrams, Micheal Egan, Elaine Turcotte, Katherine Geesey, Anthony Massarotti, Isabelle Bedrosian, Sira Konare, Anita Chang, Dana Weiss, Gerilyn Alfe, Meredith Bailey; [Alumni association] Dental school, Reunion 25 of D1934; [Alumni association] co publisher, Tufts University Photographic Portrait; [Alumni association] Co-creator of special Mastercard for Tuftonians; [Jonathan Arbanel A68] Speaker for Tufts Alliance of Chicago p. 27. Jennifer Abrams ('89). Senior Award recipient. Action Program for the Elderly 1989. Medical student volunteers. Activities and Organizations, 1989. Tufts Sailing Team, feature. Gerilyn Alfe ('89) Seniors Award recipient. Tufts Interimship program p. 26 [Alumni 1989]; [Alumni council] Elections, alumni trustees Brian O'Connell [A1953] and JoAnn Sher [J1963]
  - Criterion, Fall, 1989; UP053.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alfred A. Amendola] Recieves Ph.D.; Robert Amato [D1980] alumnus; [Alumni/ae]Juan Alvarez returned to the Dominican Republic, Contributors the New Campaign, Raelene Huck Ali [J1964], Widow of Louis Sutliff Murphy bequeaths $550,000, Leslie Gelb, John Dowling [A1959]; [Alumni/ae] Boston Tufts Alliance; [Alumni directory] Available fall 1989; [Alumni association] Jumbo club's 20th anniversary; Steven Abdulkader (F61). Senior associate in bank.; Mark Adzigian A88 (USMC) commissioned p. 42. David Abel (1987). Medical student. Elfie D. Aboulafia (G60). President-elect of surgeons. Richard Campbell Acford (A49). Died August 19, 1989. Glen Ackerman (1976). Birth of twin daughters. Katherine (Kouky) Ackerman (1977). Birth os twin daughters.; Ralph Ackley (E67). Kiled May 25, 1989, auto accident. David A. Ackroyd (M80). Medical resident. Harold Acres (1964). Guests at Freedom Foundation.; [Adzigian, David '62] Son commissioned. p. 33.; [Adzigian, Linda (Richards) J62] Son commissioned. p. 33.; [Afsar, Mohammed] Radar research, p. 13.; Mansur Ahmad [F56]. Ambassador of Pakistan. Domenic Albanese (D 86) Married. Hadi Ali (A'62) (F'64) Pakistan's Consul General. [Ali, Mehdi] [Ali, Raelene Huck (J'64) Ali Family Conference Room, Wessell; New Campaign; Wessell Library honors Mehdi and Raelene Huck Ali (J64); William Meserve A'62, (Tr.) speaker.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1990; UP053.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American dental association] Annual meeting in Honolulu; Alumni weekend; [Alumni trustee] Election candidates, Alumni elections; [Alumni relations] Tuftonia's Day; [Alumni relations] Dental school alumni association of greater New York reception. Yankee dental congress, Boston; [Alumni council] Alumni elections candidates, Continuing education committee's events; [Alumni association] Tufts club of Britain's London reception; [Alumni association] Distinguished service award recipients: Henry H. Banks [M1945], John R. Ghublikian [E1939], Jester J. Hairston [A1929][H1972], Norman B. Harris [A1938], Weston Howland Jr. (life trustee), Thomas W. Murname [A1948][D1962][K1965][G1968]; [Alumni association] Alumni council election candidates. Winter 1990
  - Criterion, Spring/Summer, 1990; UP053.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Rick Ambros [A1981] married Martha Griffith [J1981]; [Amalgamates] Tufts Alliance of South Florida host with Sam and Audrey Meline, Entertained the Atlanta Tufts Alliance; [Alumni association] Robert A. Sears articles re: elections criticized; [Alumni association] Events and benefits; [Alumni association] Fred P. Nickless scholarship fund created; [Alumni association] Global community; [Alumni association] Distinguished service awards and Senior awards; [Alumni association] Alive and well, Continuing Education committee has fun; [Alumni association] Co-sponsors Tufts Interimship program; Announces birth of daughter [Kiatro Abisinito] p. 33; Wyn Steven Adair (Faculty) died March 27, 1990. p. 36; [Adomeit, Hannes] Soviet specialist at Fletcher. p. 18.; [Adzigian, Mark A88] Completed Marine basic training. p. 34.; Aidekman Arts Center [1989-90]. Kroll, Arnold and Carolyn donate sculpture. [Akula, Vikram] Seniors Award. David Albert (1976) Birth of son. Carey E. Alexander (E '74) Appointed director of catering at Copley Plaza Hotel in Boston. Death of (1/2/90) Paul E. Allee (faculty). Reginald Alleyne Jr. (54) President of AAUP at UCLA. Thomas Alperin; [A81] launched TSR [Tufts student resources] in 1981. [Alumni Admissions Program 1990] Letter of disappointment re: financial aid, p. 38. [Alumni Advisory Board 1989-90] InterGreek Council, p. 23; [Alumni relations] Plans for winter olympics, Tufts european center
  - Criterion, Fall, 1990; UP053.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American family portraits] Feature article by Deborah Halber; [Alumni relations] Reunions and celebrations, Tuftonia's day celebrated with question of alumni as to who impacted thier lives the most; [Alumni relations]Societ union trip, Interimship program, Homecoming planned; [Alumni council] Elected Mara Glickman Aspinall [J1983], Jayne Leslie Burkhardt [J1965], John H. DeJong [A1978][V1985], Larry Diran [A1980], Marina Kalb Duboc [J1984], Edward Farley Jr. [A1957], Florence Goldman [J1938], Richard Hale [A1958], Jane Haymon [J1960], Robert Lane [E1965], Robert Mitchell [E1978], Margo Fleer Smith [J1959], Paul Tringale [A1982], Wiliam Callahan [A1958][M1962], Marcel Korn [D1966], Stephen Gucciardi [A1975][G1975], William H. Wainwright [F1965][F1967][F1972]; [Alumni association] Interimship program offered; [Alumni association] Linda Dixon, new president; Alport Benjamin [M1929] died 2/22/1990; [Alpha Omega] Dental fraternity volunteers; Wilbur Aaronson D1937 Mini-reunions p. 26. [Edith Abbate J87] married Peter Jacoby '85 p. 34. Adel Abu-moustafa. Medical School and King Abdulaziz University (KAU), Saudi Arabia, exchange. Karl Ackerman. Speaks to students regarding Vietnam War. Robert Adams (1976). Birth of second child. Arthur Addelson (1933). Died February 26, 1990. [ALagappa, Muthiah (F '84)] Confrences in Thailand. Joseph S. Ali (1967) Promoted in U.S. Public Health Service. Steve Allison (72) Married Kathleen M. Cahill. Myron Allukian Jr. (1960) President of American Public Health Association, p. 27. [Alumni 1990] Medical Alumni Weekend, p. 34. [Alumni 1990] Olympics 1992, p. 18.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1991; UP053.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American family portrait] Letter of response; Madalon Amenta [A1950] Co-author of book: Nursing care of the terminally ill; [Alumni weekend] Tribute to Edward Dugger Jr. [E1941]; [Alumni council] Ballot for Alumni trustee and alumni council; Steven Alpert [A1984] married Jan Volinsky [J84]. [Denise (Liling) Abadi] Eliot Pearson 78 relocated to Boca Raton, FL. p. 30. [Ainsworth, Harry D. (1985)] Engaged to Grace Anne Carney. Babak Alizadeh (E82, G83) Lives with wife Elizabeth (Bergl, J84) in Brookline; Announces birth of son. [Alizadeh, Elizabeth (Bergl) '84] Promoted at KPMG Peat Marwidk. [Alumni 1991] Local lights (event), p. 18. [Alumni 1991] Produce "Tufts in Song", p. 23. [Alumni 1991] Tufts College plates offered, p. 39.
  - Criterion, Spring/Summer, 1991; UP053.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. '"Come on along -- world atlas" cross country tour visiting alumni; University wide dinner; [Alumni/ae] Anonymous alumni creates graduate drama fellowship; [Alumni association] Senior awards recipients: Heather C. Adriance, Micheal D. Callahan, Jonathon C. Cutler, Keith Fitzgerald, Micheal Gilbert, Mia Luise Mask, Debra Marie O'Connell, Vera Stenhouse, Mara Youdelman; [Alpha Omega] Dental fraternity funds screening program for children of Soviet emigres; David Abel (1967). Married Curtis, Deborah.; [Dr. and Mrs. Alfred Aborjaily M53] PET Fund, private trust, medical alumni assoc. p. 18. William M. Abrams [1975]. Named a vice president at ABC-TV. Chrysantus Ache (F83). Chairman of the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees' staff council. Michael Adam (1986). Married Ellen Cosgrove.; Nicholas Agretelis [1985]. Married Joan Martin. [Admissions, Office of] Tufts Alumni Admissions Program [TAAP]. p. 16.; [Adriance, Heather] Seniors Award. p. 33. Shiley F. Aidekman. Elected charter member of trustees. [AIDS] Response to article in winter 1991 Criterion p. 34. Ainsworth, Harry D. (1985). Married Grace Carney. Ainsworth, Keith (1987). Married Julie Prescott, J87. Susanne Albertsson ('81) Married Christopher Davis. [Albright, Robert L.] (G72) Chairman of board of directors of American Council on Education. Kenneth C. Allard (F82) Author serving in the Pentagon. [Alumni 1991] Making job connections, p. 16. Tufts Alumni Admissions Program, p. 16. Elections, p. 21. Commencement Day, p. 18-19. Reunions, p. 19. [Alumni 1991] Drama/theater alumni in New York City met at WPA Theater, owned by Kyle Renick (A70), p. 17. Tufts travelouge: cross-country "trip" via Criterion, p. 3-9.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1991; UP053.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni council] Career networking committee establishes database, Interimships - learn about careers from alums, Judith A. Palais [E1956] and Gloria Spitalmy [G1972] discuss divorce and children; [Alumnae] Association of Tufts Alumna brings Tufts women together; [Marino Acera E'37] Died February 23, 1991; Charles E. Adams (F62) (A61) principal of Ware High School, Ware, MA. p. 22; [Adler, David '51] Co-Chairman for Class of 1951 reunion. P. 23. James Q. Adams (E'49). Died February 1991. Jonathan Addleton (F 82). US AID program officer in Scotland completed Fletcher dissertation.; [Adomeit, Hannes] Director of new Soviet and Central European Program at Fletcher. p. 16; Aeppel, Timothy (F'85) Joined the Bonn, Germany bureau of The Wall Street Journal, p. 30.; Gary Aidekman [A73]. Kenneth Aidekman [A75]. Shirley and Alex Aidekman Arts Center. Shirley F. Aidekman. Speaks at dedication of Shirley and Alex Aidekman Arts Center. [The New Campaign] Sackler findings could help war on AIDS. Richard Allen (D1969) Dental alumnus competes.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1992; UP053.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] Candidates vie for alumni trustee posts, Tufts black alumni association, Jewish alums organize to give Hillel a boost, Homecoming [includes photos], Alumni weekend plans, Tuftonia's day celebrations mark 8th anniversary, St. Louis alumni gathered to discuss future; [Alumni weekend] Plans for May 14-17, 1992 celebrations; [Alumni association] Continuing education enlightments series, Distinguished service award presented to six alums; Julie Alter announces birth of daughter; Annettte Altenpohl [F1984] announces birth of daughter; Dr. Leslie Alpert [G1979, M1980] Associate Professor of pathology at McGill University. [African-American Students] Black History Month comes to an end, p. 3, 8; Editorial re:enrollment, p. 4; [Agism, Frederick Dr.] Chief clinical officer at Central Ohio Psychiatric Hospital, p. 27. Nancy Alder (Feins) (79) Opened own real estate company. Kenneth C. Allard (F82) Work published. Marsha [Cowan] Alperin [A81] Announces birth of son, pg. 28. Thomas Alperin [A81] announces birth of son, pg. 28.
  - Criterion, Spring/Summer, 1992; UP053.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni weekend] Alumni relations special section: events; [Alumni relations] Alumni weekend special section on events; [Alumni council] Elections; Seth Adagala (A68) died December 3, 1991. p. 33.; [Administration] The Winning Team. A Report on The New Campaign (1987-92).; Syed Refast Ahmed [F90]. Completed year's service with United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees in Hong Kong. AIDS Quilt in Cousens Gym. [Akashi, Yasushi] Working on United Nations project in Cambodia. Akinwande Bolaji Akinyemi (F '65) Lectured to the Nigerian Society of International Affairs. [Ali, Abdu Salaam Moulta] (A'94) Islamic religion. Kenneth C. Allard (Lt. Col., USA) (F'82) Recieved the Edgar S. Furniss Book Award. Civil engineers to race in toboggan of cement.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1992; UP053.001.010.00001 (Box 10)